Trenisha Goslee

Alexandria, VA • 601-431-4921 • tgoslee@awakeningstem.com

www.linkedin.com/in/trenisha-goslee-92769358 • Portfolio: www.trenishagoslee.com

QUALIFICATIONS PROFILE

Solutions-oriented developer with a background in STEM education and instruction including programming, data structures, and software design ready to leverage training and experience in a **Web Development** or **Front End Development** role.

- **Technical Proficiencies:** Well-developed ability to utilize gather business requirements to create websites and software designed to support growth and organizational effectiveness. Proficient with emerging and established technologies to drive business transformations while meeting evolving needs.
- **Project Management:** Demonstrated ability to collaborate cross-functionally with senior leaders and colleagues to align needs with project plans. Highly organized and skilled in project planning and implementation. Results-oriented with a focus on delivering maximum impact with minimal cost. Adept at troubleshooting and resolving issues.
- **Key Strengths:** Finely tuned analytical skills utilized to improve processes to reduce redundancies and improve productivity. Value-added skills in cross-functional collaboration with the ability to explain highly technical information to non-technical project stakeholders. Easily master new and emerging technologies. Work well in independently and team-driven roles.

CORE TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React.js, Bootstrap

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS

Master of Science in Technology Education Leadership, the University of Louisiana at Monroe, Monroe, LA, 2016
Bachelor of Science in Technology Education, Old Dominion University, Norfolk, VA, 2013
The Complete Web Developer in 2020: Zero to Mastery, Udemy, Alexandria, VA 2020
Python Programming, General Assembly, Washington DC, 2020

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP, Resolve, Columbus, Ohio – Remote Engagement (5/2020 to Present)

Develop software utilizing React.js and CSS on the front end, and interacting with the back-end cloud database and server-side logic via Google Cloud Firestore/Functions for start-up organization to support functionality and end-user satisfaction.

• Collaborate cross-functionally with geographically dispersed team members to gather business requirements, identify design features, and develop applications aligned with end-user feedback and business objectives.

WEB DEVELOPER, STEM INSTRUCTOR, Awakening Stem, Washington Dc (2018 – 2019)

Designed, developed, and maintained website including writing and evaluating code structure to ensure functionality and resolve bugs and issues to facilitate positive end-user experiences. Wrote supporting code for applications. Taught Robotics, Coding, and Intro to Coding for elementary and middle school students. Average class size: 15.

- Managed and edited web page content including scheduling, overseeing contributing writer content, and publication.
 Developed style guidelines to ensure consistency, build brand awareness and create a consistent voice.
- Oversee all aspects of instructional design for STEM classes including lesson development, project assignments, and assessments to assist students in completing course goals and advancing academically.

FOUNDING STEM TEACHER, <u>Digital Pioneers Academy</u>, Washington DC (2018 – 2019)

Design and implement course syllabi including identifying educational resources, compiling course materials, and preparing assessments to ensure students successfully acquire material to meet completion requirements. Average class size: 29.

• Taught multiple STEM subjects and core Math curriculum to 6th and 7th-grade students including computer science, Lego Mindstorm Robotics, Arduino Robotics, and HTML, CSS, and Javascript for web and game design.

Trenisha Goslee

Page Two